

Contact



Phone

+91 81034 96299, 79993 82252



Website https://vishalgoud02.github.io/ personal-profile/



Email

vishalgoud81@gmail.com



Address
Vijay Nagar, Indore (Madhya
Pradesh), India

Languages

English

Conversational/Writing

Hindi

Native

Gujarati

Conversational/Reading

Education

• **M.B.A.** 2015-2017

Aasam Downtown University

B.com 2000-2003

Devi Ahilya University

Certificates

• Green Box 2010

Frameboxx, Surat

Post Graduate Deploma in 2005
 Multimedia(PGDM)

Xplora Design Skool, Indore

Tools/Software



Vishal Goud

UX UI Designer







About

I'm a Creative **UI & UX designer**, **HTML Developer**, and **WordPress developer** based in Indore (Madhya Pradesh) India. I am having 12 years of experience in relevant field.

My expertise lies in conceptualizing and designing engaging software products that are both aesthetically appealing and highly functional. With strong problem-solving abilities and skills.

I am able to deliver effective "**USER-FRIENDLY DESIGN**" solutions that satisfy the needs of both the customer and the end-user.

Experience

Sr. UX UI Designer

Imenso Software, Indore June 2017 to June 2024

As a UI/UX design team lead, I am responsible for supervising the design process and ensuring the creation of visually appealing and user-friendly products for our target audience.

Sr. UX UI Designer

Chapter247 Indore Dec 2016 to May 2017

As a Senior UI/UX Designer, my role was involves designing user-friendly interfaces through research, wireframing, and collaborating with other teams to create visually appealing products.

Sr. Web Faculty

Framebox Indore Sep 2015 to Dec 2016

I trained individuals and teams in web design and user interface development, focusing on layout, typography, color theory, and imagery to improve the user experience and website effectiveness.



Sr. Web Designer

MMF Infotech, Indore Aug 2014 to Sep 2015

As a Senior UI/UX Designer I was design user-friendly interfaces, conduct research, implement frameworks, and collaborate with cross-functional teams to create high-quality digital experiences.

Web Designer

WhitePaper, Indore Jan 2013 to July 2014

As a web designer, I used to create websites and was not charged any maintenance, along with that I also used to do graphic related work.

Soft Skills

- Conduct design research to understand user needs, develop user personas, and create a strategy based on insights and business goals.
- Focus on UX design for an intuitive product, implement adaptive design for various devices, and design seamless interactions.
- Conduct usability testing, create low to high fidelity prototypes, and use wireframing, storyboarding, and contextual research to refine concepts.
- Stay updated with UI/UX trends, design user-friendly interfaces, and create mockups for stakeholders.
- Specialize in designing mobile apps, Power BI screens, and game screens.
- I utilize AI tools and ChatGPT to enhance design and content creation, ensuring innovative, efficient, and high-quality results for various projects.
- Use 2D animation and video editing to create engaging content.